Register of the Arthur T. Vanderbilt Political, Professional, and Judicial Papers, 1902 - 1957
Arthur T. Vanderbilt Political, Professional and Judicial Papers, 1902-1957
- Bar Association Activities
  - American Bar Association: General (Box 125)
    - Committee on the Unauthorized Practice of Law, 1937-1939 (Box 127)
    - Civil Liberties, especially concerning role of the ABA (Box 127)
    - Committee on the Bill of Rights and its participation in Hague v. CIO and the first Flag Salute Case, 1939-1940 (Box 127)
    - Miscellaneous clippings (Box 127)
    - ABA Section on Legal Education (Box 128)
    - Correspondence on appointments (Box 128)
    - Hauptman Report, by a committee headed by Newton D. Baker on the unauthorized invasion of the courtroom by photographer and the impact of publicity on concept of fair trial (Box 128)
    - Junior Bar Section, correspondence, 1936-1938 (Box 128)
    - Student Bar Association, 1936-1938 (Box 128)
    - Correspondence on Appointments, 1936-1937 (Box 128)
    - Section on Legal Education (Box 128)
    - Pamphlets on Criminal Law (Box 129)
    - Section on Comparative and International Law (Box 129)
    - ABA, three folders containing correspondence on Lamb case and other matters concerning beginning of National Lawyers Guild. Correspondence with Morris L. Ernst, 1936-1938 (Box 130)
    - ABA re Federal Rules, 1936-1937 (Box 130)
    - Correspondence and reports of sections of ABA, 1937-1938 (Box 130)
    - Committee reports, 1938 (Box 130)
    - Board of Governors Agenda, 1938 (Box 131)
    - Board of Governors Proceedings, 1938-1939 (Box 131)
    - A manuscript history of ABA (Box 131)
    - Section reports, Legal Education, Judicial Administration, Admission to Bar, 1938 (Box 132)
    - Committee on Publicity; Morgan Decision; Administrative Procedure (Box 132)
    - Report on Insurance Law Section (Box 132)
    - Bar organization activities (Box 133)
    - Section on Judicial Administration, 1939 (Box 133)
    - The Ickes case (Box 133)
    - Court packing issue (Box 133)
    - Integrated Bar (Box 133)
    - Annual meetings, papers, addresses, 1938 (Box 134)
    - Lawyer referral service (Box 134)
    - Committee on Appellate Practice and Procedure (Box 134)
    - ABA Section on Judicial Administration, 1953-1957 (Box 134)
    - Section on Judicial Administration, 1941-1944 (Box 135)
    - Section on Legal Education, 1947-1951 (Box 135)
    - Committee on Peace and Law through the United Nations (Box 135)
    - Council of State Governors, 1950-1953 (Box 135)
    - Bar organization, 1944 (Box 136)
    - Actions of House of Delegates, Federal Rules; Trade Administration; Administration of Justice, 1947 (Box 136)
    - ABA Foundation, 1951 (Box 136)
    - Miscellaneous addresses (Box 136)
  - Essex County and New Jersey Bar Associations
    - New Jersey State Committee correspondence, 1948 (Box 137)
    - New Jersey State Bar Association correspondence, 1940-1947 (Box 137)
    - Essex County Bar Association correspondence, 1945-1948 (Box 137)
- Judicial Reform and the Administration of Justice, 1930-1957
  - Attorney General's Committee on Administrative Procedure, monographs and correspondence, 1941-1948 (Box 138)
  - Administrative Law
    - Miscellaneous reports, articles (Box 139)
    - ATV, "Administrative Tribunals"; answers to criticisms of S674 Hearings before subcommittee on S674, S675, 8918 (Box 139)
    - Advance Sheets (George Warren) (Box 139)
    - Report of Judicial Committee of H.R.; Report of Special Committee on Administrative Law; ATV, "100 Years of Administrative Law"; Brochure on Administrative Law, 1936-1939 (Box 140)
    - Miscellaneous articles (Box 140)
    - Clippings, 1945-1946 (Box 140)
    - Miscellaneous articles (2 folders) (Box 141)
    - Documents (Box 141)
    - Survey, clippings, bulletins (Box 141)
    - Miscellaneous materials (Box 141)
    - Advance sheets (Box 142)
    - Miscellaneous materials (Box 142)
    - Articles and printed materials, 1937-1938 (Box 142)
    - Miscellaneous materials, 1935-1939 (Box 143)
    - Attorney General's Committee, Monographs, Parts 1-13 (Box 143)
    - U.S. Attorney General's Annual Report, 1939 (Box 143)
    - Miscellaneous materials, 1939-1940 (Box 143)
    - Administrative Procedures, miscellaneous notes and materials (Box 144)
    - Miscellaneous materials (Box 144)
    - Miscellaneous pamphlets and clippings (Box 145)
    - Lectures and articles (Box 145)
    - Articles (Box 145)
    - Replies from states, 1946 (Box 145)
    - Materials for casebook (Box 145)
    - Lecture notes (Box 145)
  - New Jersey Judicial Council, 1930-1940 (Box 146)
    - First and Third Reports to Governor (Box 146)
    - Fourth and Fifth Reports (Box 146)
    - Sixth and Seventh Reports (Box 146)
    - Eighth and Final Reports (Box 146)
    - Correspondence, 1942-1947 (Box 147)
    - Assembly concurrent resolution (Box 147)
    - Reports (Box 147)
    - Statistics (Box 147)
    - State Comptroller Department (Box 147)
    - Memos re salaries of judges (Box 147)
    - Court of Pardons (Box 147)
  - National Conference of Judicial Councils (Box 148)
    - Correspondence, 1941-1943 (Box 148)
    - Correspondence, 1945-1946 (Box 149)
    - Correspondence, 1946 (Box 150)
    - Correspondence, 1947-1950 (Box 151)
    - Account #1, 1938-1947 (Box 152)
    - Account #2, 1938-1946 (Box 152)
    - Account #2, 1947-1950 (Box 152)
    - Account #2, 1938-1947 (Box 152)
    - Account #2, 1951 (Box 152)
    - Miscellaneous books paid for, 1948-1950 (Box 152)
    - Acknowledgement of Handbook of New Jersey (Box 152)
    - Correspondence re Judicial Administration Section (2 folders) (Box 153)
    - Automobile Manufacturing Association (Box 153)
    - By-Laws, annual programs, addresses (Box 153)
    - Annual handbook of NCJC, 1940-1942 (Box 153)
    - Reviews of ATV Minimum Standards of Judicial Administration (Box 153)
  - Advisory Committee of United States Supreme Court on Federal Rules of Criminal Procedure (Box 154)
    - Correspondence, 1944-1953 (Box 154)
    - Committee Reports, preliminary drafts, rules, notes (Box 155)
    - Federal pamphlets (Box 155)
    - Federal criminal procedures, notes (Box 155)
    - Ohio--experiments in measurements of judicial qualification in Supreme Court of Ohio (Box 155)
  - Committee on Military Justice for the War Department, 1946-1950 (Box 156)
    - Correspondence, 1946-1950 (Box 156)
    - Hearings of War Department Advisory Committee, 1946 (Box 157)
    - Report of hearings (Box 157)
    - Bibliography lists (NYU) Topical outlines (Box 157)
    - Advisory Committee, 1946 (Box 158)
    - Regional hearings (summaries of testimonies), 1946 (Box 158)
    - Criminal Law (Box 158)
    - Miscellaneous materials on military justice (Box 158)
    - Miscellaneous materials (Box 159)
  - National Committee on Traffic Law Enforcement (Box 160)
    - Correspondence, 1938-1943 (Box 160)
    - Correspondence, 1946 (Box 161)
    - Correspondence, 1940-1951 (Box 161)
    - Speeches ATV and George Warren publicity, 1940-1943 (Box 161)
    - Emergency traffic law enforcement program, 11/4/41 (Box 161)
    - Subcommittee on model legislation, 1941-1942 (Box 161)
    - Committee member lists and acceptances, 1939 (Box 161)
    - Traffic enforcement clippings, 1916 (Box 161)
    - Lists of members, questionnaires, meetings, progress reports, and paid bills Trenton office, 1938-1043 (Box 161)
    - Correspondence, 1941-1951 (Box 162)
    - Publishing list for Traffic Courts (Box 162)
  - Hoover Commission on Reorganization of the Government (Box 163)
    - News releases, reports (Box 163)
    - Early drafts of reports of Task Force on Legal Service and Procedures (Box 163)
    - Minutes, notices of meetings, miscellaneous minutes on Task Force (Box 163)
    - Early drafts of Reports of Task Force (Box 163)
    - Correspondence, 1950-1953, 1954-1957 (Box 164)
    - Miscellaneous materials (Box 164)
  - New Jersey Constitutional Revision Movement:, 1940-1948 (Box 165)
    - Constitutional Revision Commission minutes, drafts, memos, 1941-1942 (Box 165)
    - Pamphlets, 1941-1942 (Box 165)
    - Constitutional Revision Commission Clippings, 1941-1944 (Box 166)
    - Constitutional Revision Commission Documents, drafts, 1942 (Box 166)
    - Constitutional Revision Commission, Drafts, booklets, 1944 (Box 166)
    - Constitutional Revision Commission, Committee on Chancery Court Rules (Box 166)
    - Public hearings, Feb. 3, 1944 (Box 167)
    - Clippings, 1944-1947 (Box 167)
    - Constitutional Convention Proceedings, 1947 (Box 168)
    - Transcripts of Committee Proceedings (Box 169)
    - Committee on Judiciary (Box 169)
    - Committee on Executive, Militia, and Civil Affairs (Box 169)
    - Transcripts of Committee Proceedings (Box 170)
    - Committee on Taxation and Finances (Box 170)
    - Committee on Legislature (Box 170)
    - Committee on Rights, Privileges, Amendments, and Miscellaneous Provisions (Box 170)
    - Temple Report on Constitutional Revision (3 folders) (Box 171)
    - Harrison Reports on Constitutional Revision (Box 172)
    - Governor Committee Reports (2 folders) (Box 172)
    - Reports to Governor on Constitution Revision (Box 173)
    - Miscellaneous materials on constitutional convention (5 folders) historical infirmities, pamphlets, reports, cartoons, memos, opinions, minutes, etc. (Box 174)
- Chief Justice of New Jersey:, 1948-1957
  - Opinions (Box 175)
    - Docket Books, 1948-1951 (Box 175)
    - Docket Books, 1952-1955 (Box 176)
    - Opinions; Clippings, briefs, correspondence, drafts, 1948-1950 (Box 177)
    - Opinions terms (including Trenton Six case), 1949 (Box 178)
    - Opinions (including Winberry v. Salisbury), 1950 (Box 179)
    - Opinions, 1951 (Box 180)
    - Opinions, 1951 (Box 181)
    - Opinions, 1952 (Box 182)
    - Opinions, 1952 (Box 183)
    - Opinions, 1953 (Box 184)
    - Opinions (including Tudor v. Board of Education of Rutherford), 1953 (Box 185)
      [Missing as of January 1999.]
    - Opinions, 1954 (Box 186)
    - Opinions, 1955 (Box 187)
    - Opinions, 1955-1956 (Box 188)
    - Opinions, 1956 (Box 189)
  - Correspondence (Box 190)
    - Miscellaneous, 1947-1951 (Box 190)
    - Miscellaneous, 1947-1951 (Box 191)
    - Congratulatory exchanges, 1947-1957 (Box 192-193)
    - General, 1947-1957 (Box 194-195)
    - General, 1952-1957 (Box 196)
    - Correspondence with New Jersey Justices of Supreme Court and Judges of Superior Courts, 1947-1954 (Box 197-198)
    - Correspondence with Justices of Supreme Court and Judges of Superior Courts, 1954-1957 (Box 199-202)
    - Correspondence, organized in folders by states, 1955-1957 (Box 203-204)
    - Correspondence on law reform developments with other judges, lawyers, journalists, by states (Box 205-206)
    - Correspondence re Conferences of Chief Justices, 1048-1957 (Box 207)
    - Memos and miscellaneous materials (Box 207)
    - Habeas corpus, 1952 (Box 207)
    - Correspondence, miscellaneous, 1948-1957 (Box 208-209)
  - Clipping Files (Box 210)
    - Administrative Law (Box 210)
    - Admissions to Bar (Box 210)
    - Adoption--see Divorce, custody, etc. (Box 210)
    - Attorney General Richman (Box 210)
    - Bar Associations--N.J., out-of-state (Box 210)
    - Bingo (Box 210)
    - Books (Box 210)
    - Cases: (Box 210)
      - Atlantic City Investigation (Box 210)
      - Baldwin Case (Box 210)
      - Burlington Bridges (Box 210)
      - Frank Hague (Box 210)
      - Gideon's Bible (Box 210)
      - Hale Decision (Box 210)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 210)
      - Nappe v. Nappe (Box 210)
      - Public Service Rate (Box 210)
      - Toth Case (Box 210)
      - Trenton Six (Box 210)
      - Winberry--see Rule-making (Box 210)
      - Winne (Box 210)
    - Cases out of state (Box 210)
    - Sunday Law Case (Box 210)
    - Citizenship Clearing House (Box 210)
    - Clerkships--see Admissions to Bar (Box 210)
    - Connecticut Court System (Box 210)
    - Constitutional Law (Box 210)
    - Constitutional Revision (Box 210)
    - County Courts (Box 211)
    - Court Clerks (Box 211)
    - County Park Commissioners (Box 211)
    - Court Funds (Box 211)
    - Court Rooms and Chambers (Box 211)
    - Court Statistics (Box 211)
    - Court Stenographers (Box 211)
    - Crime--criminal law and justice (Box 211)
    - Delays in Court (Box 211)
    - Divorce and Custody of Children (Box 211)
    - Driscoll, Governor (Box 211)
    - Education--General (Box 211)
    - Education for government (Box 211)
    - Education-legal and prelegal (Box 211)
    - Ethics, legal (Box 211)
    - Evidence and Committee on (Box 211)
    - Federal Government (Box 211)
    - Ford Foundation and Report (Box 211)
    - International Affairs (Box 211)
    - Judges--general (Box 211)
    - Judges--NJ appointments (Box 211)
    - Judges--NJ Individually A-H (Box 211)
    - Judges--New Jersey I-Z (Box 211)
    - Judicial Administration--general (Box 212)
    - Judicial Administration--NJ (Box 212)
    - Judicial Conferences, NJ, 1948-1957 (Box 212)
    - Juries--general (Box 212)
    - Jury, grand (Box 212)
    - Juvenile Delinquency, 1948-1957 (Box 212)
    - Legal Aid (Box 212)
    - Legislation and Ordinances (Box 212)
    - Legal Profession (Box 212)
    - Lloyd, Judge Frank T., Jr. (Box 212)
    - Local Courts (Box 212)
    - Loyalty Oath (Box 212)
    - Meyner, Governor (Box 212)
    - Military Justice (Box 212)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 212)
    - Politics (Box 213)
    - Pretrial conferences (Box 213)
    - Probation (Box 213)
    - Railroad passes (Box 213)
    - Rule-making (Box 213)
    - Rules, NJ (Box 213)
    - Rutgers University (Box 213)
    - Salaries and pensions (Box 213)
    - Seton Hall University (Box 213)
    - Statute Revision, Titles 2 and 3 (Box 213)
    - Strikes and Unions (Box 213)
    - Traffic (Box 213)
    - Workmen's Compensation (Box 213)
  - Subject Files (Box 214)
    - Administrative Director--Willard Woelper, 1948-1954 (Box 214)
    - Administrative Law, correspondence, 1941-1954 (Box 214)
    - American Airlines (Box 215)
    - American Warehousemen's Association (Box 215)
    - American Arbitration Association (Box 215)
    - American Journal of Legal History (Box 215)
    - American Judicature Society (Box 215)
    - American Political Science Association on Judicial Organization and Administration (Box 215)
    - American Political Science Association (3 folders) (Box 215)
    - American Society for Legal History (Box 215)
    - Appeals, appendices on (Box 216)
    - Appeals by the state in criminal cases (Box 216)
    - Appellate practice (Box 216)
    - Atlantic City Investigation--Judge Lloyd (Box 217)
    - Attorney General Committee to July, 1955 (Box 217)
    - Attorney General's Committee on Elimination of Delay in the Court (Box 217)
    - Authorities (Box 217)
    - Bar Association Camden County, Union, Essex (Box 217)
    - Bar Association Hudson, Bergen, Passaic (Box 217)
    - Bar Association Monmouth, Mercer, Ocean (Box 217)
    - Bar Association Atlantic, Sommerset, Glouster (Box 218)
    - Bar Association New Jersey (Box 218)
    - Bar Examination (Box 218)
    - Bar Integration (Box 218)
    - Bergen County Stamler Investigation (Box 218)
    - Briefs, Committee on (Box 218)
    - Budget, 1947-1952 (Box 218)
    - Character and Fitness Committee (Box 218)
    - Clerk of the Superior Court (Box 219)
    - Clerk of the Supreme Court (Box 219)
    - Clerkships Committee (Box 219)
    - Constitutional Law (Box 219)
    - Counsellors Course (Box 219)
    - County Courts (Box 219)
    - County Courts--constitutional amendment (Box 219)
    - County clerks (Box 219)
    - County judges (Box 219)
    - County Park Commissioners (Box 219)
    - County Prosecutors (Box 220)
    - Court Stenographers (Box 220)
    - Court Clerks and Law Section (Box 220)
    - Court photographers (Box 220)
    - Committee on Evidence (Box 220)
    - Criminal Law and Committee on Improving Criminal Justice, 1948-l953 (Box 220)
    - Criminal forms (Box 220)
    - Criminal Law (Box 221)
    - Criminal Procedure--review of rules of (Box 221)
    - District Court Procedure (Box 221)
    - District Court--Committee on (Box 221)
    - District Court Legislation (Box 221)
    - District Courts (Box 221)
    - Federal Taxation (Box 221)
    - Ford Foundation Report on Adult Education (Box 222)
    - Miscellaneous materials, drafts, etc. (Box 222)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, clippings (Box 222)
    - Ford Foundation correspondence (Box 223)
    - Guardian ad litem (Box 224)
    - Habeas Corpus proceedings (Box 224)
    - Hadji-Bira, John (Box 224)
    - Humor (judicial) (Box 224)
    - International Law (Box 224)
    - Committee on procedure for adjudication of insanity and commitments of mental incompetents (Box 224)
    - Judges, absences (Box 224)
    - Judges, annual dinner (Box 224)
    - Judges of New Jersey. deceased (Box 224)
    - Judges salaries and pension (Box 224)
    - Judges sections and tenure (Box 224)
    - Judicial aspirants (Box 224)
    - Judge Norman T. Rogers (Box 225)
    - Judges retired or deceased (Box 225)
    - Judicial--Assignment of judges (Box 225)
    - Judicial administration--pamphlets, articles, correspondence (8 files) (Box 226)
    - Judicial Conference (2 files), Sept. 13, 1948 (Box 227)
    - Judicial Conference(2 files), 1949 (Box 227)
    - Judicial Conference (2 files), 1950 (Box 228)
    - Judicial Conference, 1951 (Box 228)
    - Judicial Conference, 1952 (Box 229)
    - Judicial Conference, 1957 (Box 229)
    - Miscellaneous Materials on Judicial Conferences (Box 229)
    - Judicial--Miscellaneous (Box 230)
    - Judicial--Pensions (Box 230)
    - Juries and grand juries (Box 230)
    - Juries and Jurors--committee on (Box 230)
    - Jurisprudence (Box 230)
    - Jury commission (Box 230)
    - Jury Commissioner--Atlantic County (Box 230)
    - Juries--materials re Constitutional Provision (Box 231)
    - Jury selection (Box 231)
    - Juvenile Delinquency--independent commission (Box 232)
    - Articles, pamphlets (Box 232)
    - Correspondence, 1951-1957 (Box 232)
    - Juvenile and Domestic Relations Court (Box 232)
    - Juvenile Court judgeships (Box 232)
    - Juvenile and Domestic Relations Court--correspondence (Box 233)
    - Junior Bar Conference Traffic Program (Box 233)
    - Journal of Legal Education (Box 233)
    - John Marshall Bicentennial Commission (Box 233)
    - Joint Conference on Professional Responsibility (Box 233)
    - John Boynton Kaiser (Newark librarian) (Box 233)
    - Legal Profession--practice of law (Box 233)
    - Law Reform, methods of (Box 234)
    - Lawyer's Indemnity Fund (Box 234)
    - Law Enforcement Council (Box 234)
    - Legal Aid Correspondence, 1952-1957 (Box 234)
    - Legal Education (N.J. Law Schools) (Box 234)
    - Legal Histories (Box 234)
    - Legal Ethics (Ethics and Grievance Committee), 1948-1957 (Box 235)
    - Legal Education (Box 235)
    - Legislation (2 folders) (Box 236)
    - Legislation, 1948 (Box 236)
    - Legislation, 1949 (Box 237)
    - Legislative news and index (Box 237)
    - Legislation, 1950 (Box 237)
    - Legislation, 1951 (Box 237)
    - Legislation, Revision of Titles II, III (Box 238)
    - Legislation, 1952 (Box 238)
    - Legislation, 1953 (Box 238)
    - Legislation, 1954-1957 (Box 239)
    - Local Courts, 1948 (Box 240)
    - Magistrates Conference, 1948-1951 (Box 240)
    - Magistrates Conference, 1955-1956 (Box 241)
    - Municipal Courts (2 folders) (Box 241)
    - Matrimonial Proceedings (Box 241)
    - Committee on Divorce and Custody of Children (Box 241)
    - Committee on Marital Desertion (Box 241)
    - Matrimonial. Committee on Divorce Reconciliation (Box 242)
    - Matrimonial Proceedings (2 folders) (Box 242)
    - Marx Lectures (University of Cincinnati Law School, 1957) (Box 243)
    - Marine Maintenance Corp. (Box 243)
    - Governor Heyner, 1954-1957 (Box 243)
    - Minimum Standards of Judicial Administration (Box 243)
    - Museum of Government Arts and Science (Box 243)
    - New Jersey Law Institute (Box 244)
    - New Jersey Judicial History and Progress (Box 244)
    - New Jersey Law Journal (Box 244)
    - New Jersey Law Journal, 1951-1952 (Box 244)
    - Committee on Incarceration of Narcotic Victims (Box 244)
    - Pepsi-Cola, miscellaneous (Box 244)
    - Politics, 1948 (Box 244)
    - Pretrial Practice, correspondence, 1948-1952 (Box 245)
    - Committee on Pretrial Practice and Calendar Control (Box 245)
    - Pretrial Practice Correspondence, 1953-1957 (Box 245)
    - Oaths (Box 245)
    - Orders and Decrees (Box 245)
    - Presidential Conference on Administrative Procedure (Box 245)
    - Picketing of Courts (Box 245)
    - Phi Beta Kappa--drafts of articles: "The Neglected Glory of PBK," "PBK: 1776-1951," "An Example to Emulate." (Box 246)
    - Correspondence, 1942 (Box 246)
    - Phi Beta Kappa Correspondence, 1942-1953 (Box 247)
    - Probation File (Box 248)
    - Property (Box 248)
    - Prudential Insurance Co. (Box 248)
    - Prudential Insurance Co. Tax Legislation (Box 248)
    - Publication of Rules and Opinions (Box 248)
    - Public Law (Box 248)
    - Public Relations (Box 248)
    - Publications of Opinions, Committee on (Box 248)
    - Revision of Titles 2 and 3. Senator Clapp's Committee (Box 248)
    - Rules Adopted March 16, 1953 as a remodel of the Passage of SI-S54 (Box 249)
    - Rules Amendment Title 2 and 3 (Box 249)
    - Rule-making power (Box 249)
    - Rutgers University, 1948-1953 (Box 249)
    - Rutgers University Law School (Box 250)
    - Scribes (Box 250)
    - Schwartz, Bernard (Box 250)
    - Committee on Sentencing (Box 250)
    - Seton Hall University School of Law, 1948-1957 (Box 250)
    - Society of Public Teachers of Law (Box 250)
    - Southwestern at Memphis (Box 250)
    - Stassen, Harold (Box 251)
    - Statistcs, Judicial, 1948-1949 (Box 251)
    - Statistics, Judicial, 1948-1947 (Box 252)
    - Statistics, 1949-1952 (Box 253)
    - Supreme Court of New Jersey, form letters and questionnaires, 1948-1949 (Box 253)
    - Supreme Court (Box 253)
    - Statute Revision Bills (Box 254)
    - Statute Revision General (Box 254)
    - Summers Bill--Removal of Judges, l938 (Box 254)
    - Superior Court (Box 254)
    - Court Stationery (Box 254)
    - Surrogates (Box 254)
    - Swearing in, September 13, 1948 (Box 254)
    - Testimony, expert medical (Box 255)
    - Traffic Law and Codes (Box 255)
    - Traffic, Gov. Meyner (Box 255)
    - Traffic Court Correspondence (Box 255)
    - Training for the Practice of Lawyers Committee (Box 255)
    - United States Courts (Box 255)
    - Uniform Laws (Box 255)
    - Unauthorized Practice of Law (Box 255)
    - Letters concerning office of United States Chief (Box 255)
    - Justice and Justice, 1953, 1954 (Box 255)
    - ATV Judicial Chambers Telephone Records, 1948 (Box 256)
    - Telephone memos, 1946-1948 (Box 256)
    - Telephone calls, 1951-1954 (Box 256)
    - White Laboratories (Box 256)
    - Workmen's Compensation (Box 256)
- Folders of Engagements (Correspondence, Addresses, Photos)
  - Engagements, 1938-1941 (Box 257)
  - Engagements, 1940-1941 (Box 258)
  - Engagements, 1942-1943 (Box 259)
  - Engagements, 1945-1948 (Box 260)
  - Engagements, 1947-1948 (Box 261)
  - Engagements, 1945-1948 (Box 262)
  - Engagements, 1950-1951 (Box 263)
  - Engagements, 1950-1951 (Box 264)
  - Engagements, 1952-1954 (Box 265)
  - Engagements, 1952-1954 (Box 266)
  - Engagements, 1952-1954 (Box 267)
  - Engagements [See also Container No. 307], 1957 (Box 268)
  - Engagements not attended, 1957 (Box 268)
  - "Brief for a Better Court System" (Box 268)
  - Harvard Law School Association of New Jersey, Feb. 23, 1956 (Box 269)
  - Bar Association of New Jersey Correspondence [See also Container No. 137 for 1940-1947], 1948-1951 (Box 269)
  - Invitations declined, 1949-1955 (Box 270)